

masonlee.me

mason.mideumlee@gmail.com

+1 (778) 898-4759

### **Education**

2010.01 - 2014.12 Simon Fraser University

Vancouver, Canada

Bachelor of Science

Major: Interactive Art and Technology, Design Concentration

Minor: Biomedical Physiology and Kinesiology

# Skill

Design		Programming
Framer.js	Design research/evaluation	HTML
Sketch	Understanding users	CSS
Axure	Wireframes	JQuery
Adobe Photoshop	Prototypes	
Adobe Illustrator	A/B testing	
Adobe Indesign	Visual interface design	

## Experience

2015.01 - Current San Francisco, CA

#### AdHusky - Designer

AdHusky provides one stop Facebook ad solution for small business owners. As of April 2015 AdHusky helped more than 2000 small business owners to reach out to their customers by Facebook.

About I first met two founders while working at a StartX portfolio company and

remotely helped the team since September 2013. On January 2015, I moved to San Francisco to join the team as soon as I finished my degree.

Responsibilities Redesigned the company website (adhusky.com) and web application (app.adhusky.com) while defining task flows, design patterns, site maps

and building wireframes and prototypes.

Utilized Bootstrap as a framework.



masonlee.me



mason.mideumlee@gmail.com



+1 (778) 898-4759

2014.05 - 2014.08 Vancouver, BC

#### Samsung Electronics Canada - User Experience Designer

Worked with UX researchers, interaction designers, visual designers and front-end engineers in improving the website and applications of Samsung KNOX (a mobile security solution and mobile device management software).

Responsibilities

Designed tasks and questionnaires for the usability study.

Moderated the usability study with participants.

Compiled, analyzed, and presented research findings - both

quantitative and qualitative.

Made video clips of the study to show research findings. Built prototypes that was used in 23 usability studies.

Designed internal UX research newsletter.

2013.06 - 2013.08

#### **Linknovate - Designer**

Palo Alto, CA Linknovate is a startup helping companies reduce their time-to-market

cycles and to boost their R&D capabilities by building ecosystems,

such as search engines.

About

Worked while the company was in the StartX accelerator program.

Responsibilities

Helped with designing and developing website from the initial stage.

Designed and built the front-end of the company website.

Created wireframes and prototypes.



#### Wix Hackathon San Francisco - Winning Team

Integrated simple Facebook advertising process into the Wix Dashboard.

### Startup Weekend Vancouver 2014 - Winners of the Spring Prize for **Best Purpose-driven Startup and Third Place Overall**

Formed a team called Votely, where we pitched an idea of developing a tool that allows young, disengaged voters to rapidly and intuitively get matched with political candidates whose views and priorities best align with their own.